A Guide to the Taconic Foundation records FA407
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1958-2010; 1; 76.73 Cubic Feet 172 document boxes (including 1 half-box), 2 oversized flat boxes; 2.02 Gigabytes 35 digital files
  - Literacy Assistance Center, Inc.
    - 1983-1988 (Box 72, Folder 732)
    - 1989-1995 (Box 73, Folder 733)
    - 2002 (Box 73, Folder 734)
    - (Literature), 1991 (Box 73, Folder 735)
    - (Literature), 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 736)
  - LItow, Stanley, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 737)
    Correspondence file. For earlier correspondence, see Interface.
  - Little Red Schoolhouse - Elizabeth Irwin High School (New York), 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 738)
    Support for a teacher workshop in British primary school methods.
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC)
    Support for community and housing development programs.
    - 1981, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 739)
    - 1987 (Box 73, Folder 740)
    - 1988 (Box 73, Folder 741)
    - 1989 January-September (Box 73, Folder 742)
    - 1989 October - 1990 March (Box 73, Folder 743)
    - 1990 April - 1991 (Box 74, Folder 744)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 745)
    - 1996-2000 (Box 74, Folder 746)
    - 2001 (Box 74, Folder 747)
    - 2002 (Box 74, Folder 748)
    - 2003 (Box 74, Folder 749)
    - 2004 (Box 74, Folder 750)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 751)
  - Lower Bucks County Young Men's Christian Association, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 752)
    Grant for Hell's Black Cobras, in recognition of the youth group's contribution to the improvement of urban life.
  - Lower East Side Family Union
    - 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 753)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 754)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 75, Folder 755)
    - 1980-1984 (Box 75, Folder 756)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 75, Folder 757)
  - Lower East Side Girls Club of New York, 1999-2002 (Box 75, Folder 758)
  - Lower East Side Girls Club of New York, 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 759)
  - Lower East Side Mutual Housing Association, Inc., 1989 (Box 75, Folder 760)
  - Lower East Side Mutual Housing Association, Inc., 1990-1993 (Box 75, Folder 761)
  - Low Income Housing Fund / Low Income Investment Fund
    In late 2002, the organization's name changed from Low Income Housing Fund to Low Income Investment Fund.
    - 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 762)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 763)
    - 1994 (Box 76, Folder 764)
    - 1995 (Box 76, Folder 765)
    - 1996-1999 (Box 76, Folder 766)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 76, Folder 767)
    - 2003 (Box 76, Folder 768)
    - 2004 (Box 76, Folder 769)
    - 2005 (Box 76, Folder 770)
  - Low Income Housing Information Service
    Correspondents include Cushing Dolbeare and Mary Brooks.
    Cushing N. Dolbeare was executive secretary of the Low Income Housing Information Service, an organization founded in 1977 to provide information and analysis on Federal housing policy and programs. The Low Income Housing Information Service was succeeded by the National Low Income Housing Coalition.
    - 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 771)
    - 1978-1981 (Box 77, Folder 772)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 77, Folder 773)
    - 1985-1990 (Box 77, Folder 774)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 77, Folder 775)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 776)
      - The Housing Poster, 1993; 2014:FA407:008 (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:008)
  - Magat, Richard, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 777)
    Correspondence concerning his research on relationships between organized labor and philanthropy, and Taconic Foundation grantmaking.
  - Manhattan Country School, 1965-1975 (Box 77, Folder 778)
  - Manhattan Country School, 1976-1988 (Box 77, Folder 779)
  - Marriage and Family Research Project
    Study on Catholic Marriage and Birth Control in the United States. Correspondents include Mathew Ahmann and Hazel R. and Sidney Firstman.
    - 1964-1966 (Box 77, Folder 780)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 78, Folder 781)
  - Masters Children's Center (of the Masters Nursery), 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 782)
    Support for study on "The Development of Intelligence in Schizophrenic Children and a Control Group of Normal Toddlers." Margaret Mahler is principal investigator.
  - Masters Children's Center (of the Masters Nursery), 1962-1963, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 783)
  - Mead Housing Trust, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 784)
    Support for the Urban Workshop's contribution to the improvement of urban life.
    Mead Housing Trust, Los Angeles, CA.
  - Mellen, Joan, 1979-1982 (Box 78, Folder 785)
    Correspondence concerning her biographical study of the Bruce family.
  - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1982, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 786)
  - Metropolitan Action Institute
    The Metropolitan Action Institute was formerly known as the Suburban Action Institute. The Suburban Action Institute had focused on exclusionary zoning practices that prevented people from moving out of inner-city areas. Its 1980 name change to Metropolitan Action Institute reflected its new focus on the displacement arising from gentrification and urban economic revitalization.
    For materials prior to 1980, see Suburban Action Institute.
    - 1980-1982 (Box 78, Folder 787)
    - 1983 (Box 78, Folder 788)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 78, Folder 789)
  - Metropolitan Applied Research Center (MARC): General, 1967-1974 (Box 78, Folder 790)
  - Metropolitan Applied Research Center (MARC): Conference of Black Elected Officials, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 791)
  - Metropolitan Applied Research Center (MARC): Education Program, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 792)
  - Metropolitan Community Aid Council, 1968-1970 (Box 79, Folder 793)
    Support for Homer Project in Washington, D.C.; also called "Jobs, Housing and Soldiers."
  - Metropolitan New York Center for Education in Politics, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 794)
    Materials concern the Center's internship program, directed by Robert S. Hirschfield, Hunter College.
  - Metropolitan Washington Planning and Housing Association. See Washington Planning and Housing Association.
  - MFY Legal Services, 2006-2007 (Box 79, Folder 795)
    MFY Legal Services began in 1963 as the legal arm of the anti-poverty organization, Mobilization for Youth. In 1968 it became an independent non-profit organization.
    Support for the License to Work Initiative to help ex-offenders re-enter the workplace.
  - Miles College, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 796)
  - Ministerial Interfaith Association
    The Ministerial Interfaith Association was a community and social action organization working through local churches in Harlem, NY.
    - 1965-1967 (Box 79, Folder 797)
    - 1968-1970, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 798)
    - (Literature), 1968-1969, undated (Box 79, Folder 799)
  - Mission Rebels in Action, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 800)
    Grant made to San Francisco organization in recognition of its contribution to the improvement of urban life.
  - Mobilization for Youth, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 801)
  - Morningside Community Center
    - 1961-1964 (Box 79, Folder 802)
    - 1965, 1968-1970 (Box 79, Folder 803)
    - (Literature), 1960-1963 (Box 79, Folder 804)
    - (Literature), 1964-1969 (Box 80, Folder 805)
      - Young children in classroom, youths painting railing, and "Morningside Conservation … " demonstration, 1960s; 2014:FA407:035; 6 still images (Item 2014:FA407:035)
  - Morris Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association
    - 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 806)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 80, Folder 807)
    - 1977 (Box 80, Folder 808)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 80, Folder 809)
  - Motley, R. Susan, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 810)
    The file includes two papers by Motley on community development, and an invitation to join the board of the Taconic Foundation.
  - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1966, 1969, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 811)
    Includes 1969 address on "Architecture in a Time of Trouble."
  - Municipal Art Society of New York
    - 1988-1990 (Box 80, Folder 812)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 80, Folder 813)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 80, Folder 814)
  - Muskie Bill re: Lobbying, 1971-1972 (Box 80, Folder 815)
    Correspondence concerning the Muskie-Scott bill (S-3063), giving charitable organizations the right to communicate with legislative bodies.
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund: General
    - 1961-1966 (Box 81, Folder 816)
    - 1968-1969, 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 817)
      - Broadside, "In Danger! 32 Years of Human Rights Progress", 1972 October; 2014:FA407:009 (Item 2014:FA407:009)
        Reprinted from the New York Times, October 1, 1972. Enclosed with notes from Briefing Session, October 6, 1972.
    - 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder 818)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 819)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 81, Folder 820)
    - 1990-1992 (Box 81, Folder 821)
    - 1996 (Box 81, Folder 822)
    - (Literature), 1971-1983 (Box 81, Folder 823)
      Includes motion and supplemental order in Adams v. Weinberger, 1974, concerning HEW compliance with Title VI; and Summary of Proceedings, Metropolitan School Desegregation Conference, Washington, DC, December 4-5, 1970.
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Equal Educational Opportunities for Black and Other Minority Groups (Title VI)
    Support for litigation to compel HEW compliance with Title VI of the 1964 Civil Rights Act in regard to school desegregation.
    - 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 824)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 82, Folder 825)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Zoning - Housing Program
    Grants in 1970 and 1972 targeted exclusionary land use practices in regard to housing; support in subsequent years addressed discriminatory practices in housing more generally.
    - 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 826)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 827)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 82, Folder 828)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 82, Folder 829)
    - 1982-1985 (Box 82, Folder 830)
  - NAACP Special Contribution Fund: General
    - 1964, 1966-1968, 1971-1976 (Box 82, Folder 831)
    - 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 832)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 833)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 83, Folder 834)
    - 1988-1990 (Box 83, Folder 835)
  - NAACP Special Contribution Fund: Mississippi, 1976-1979 (Box 83, Folder 836)
  - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials (NAIRO), 1960-1969 (Box 83, Folder 837)
  - National Association of Student Planners and Architects, 1968-1969 (Box 83, Folder 838)
  - National Capital Housing Authority (Regency House Project), 1969-1970 (Box 83, Folder 839)
  - National Catholic Conference for Interracial Justice: Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 83, Folder 840)
    Correspondence filed under headings of "General" and "Project Equality."
  - National Catholic Conference for Interracial Justice: Correspondence, 1961-1967 (Box 83, Folder 841)
    Correspondence filed under headings "Urban Housing" and "Southern Field Service."
  - National Catholic Conference for Interracial Justice: Program Reports
    - General, 1962-1966 (Box 84, Folder 842)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 843)
    - General (Proposal to Ford Foundation), 1967 (Box 84, Folder 844)
    - Employment Services, 1964-1965 (Box 84, Folder 845)
    - Financial Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 846)
    - Southern Field Service Project, 1961-1964 (Box 84, Folder 847)
    - Southern Field Service Project, 1965-1969 (Box 84, Folder 848)
  - National Center for Community Law, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 849)
  - National Child Labor Committee
    Organization was formerly known as the National Committee on Employment of Youth.
    - 1975 (Box 84, Folder 850)
    - 1976 (Box 84, Folder 851)
    - 1980-1982, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 852)
  - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1965-1970 (Box 85, Folder 853)
  - National Coalition on Black Voter Participation
    - 1983-1985 April (Box 85, Folder 854)
    - 1985 May-December (Box 85, Folder 855)
    - 1986-1987 May (Box 85, Folder 856)
    - 1987 June-December (Box 85, Folder 857)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 85, Folder 858)
  - National Committee against Discrimination in Housing: General
    - 1964-1966 (Box 85, Folder 859)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 860)
    - 1972 (Box 85, Folder 861)
      Meeting on March 2, 1972, to present results of the NCDH's study of jobs and housing for racial minorities in the suburban areas of the New York metropolitan region.
    - 1973-1978 (Box 86, Folder 862)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 86, Folder 863)
    - 1985 January-September (Box 86, Folder 864)
      File includes a manuscript copy of the Committee's Fair Housing Law Manual, April 1985.
    - 1985 October - 1988 (Box 86, Folder 865)
  - National Committee against Discrimination in Housing: Fair Housing / Referendum, 1964-1965 (Box 86, Folder 866)
    Support for the National Legal Conference on Equal Opportunity in Housing, Berkeley, February 5-6, 1965, to examine issues relating to Fair Housing and the Referendum Process.
  - National Committee against Discrimination in Housing: Washington Office, 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 867)
  - National Committee for the Day Care of Children, 1960-1962 (Box 86, Folder 868)
  - National Committee for the Day Care of Children, 1963-1965 (Box 86, Folder 869)
  - National Committee on Employment of Youth, 1959-1965, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 870)
    For later materials see National Child Labor Committee.
  - National Conference on State Parks, 1965-1966 (Box 86, Folder 871)
  - National Council for the Panel of Americans, 1957-1959 (Box 86, Folder 872)
  - National Council for the Panel of Americans, 1960-1965 (Box 87, Folder 873)
  - National Council of Negro Women: Conference and General, 1969-1972, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 874)
  - National Council of Negro Women: Educational Foundation (Wednesdays in Mississippi Project), 1962-1964 (Box 87, Folder 875)
  - National Council of Negro Women: Educational Foundation (Wednesdays in Mississippi Project), 1965-1966 (Box 87, Folder 876)
  - National Council of Negro Women: Literature, 1965-1968 (Box 87, Folder 877)
  - National Council of Women of the United States, 1958, 1961-1966 (Box 87, Folder 878)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Freedom School Program), 1968-1970 (Box 87, Folder 879)
    Matching grant for the Eastern High School Freedom Corporation, in Washington, DC.
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions: General
    - 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 880)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 87, Folder 881)
    - 1999 (Box 87, Folder 882)
    - 2000 (Box 88, Folder 883)
    - 2001 (Box 88, Folder 884)
    - 2002 (Box 88, Folder 885)
    - 2003 (Box 88, Folder 886)
    - 2004 (Box 88, Folder 887)
    - 2005 (Box 88, Folder 888)
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions: Lower East Side People's Federal Credit Union, 1990, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 889)
  - National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers, 1974-1975, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 890)
  - National Housing and Human Development Alliance
    Community Programs, Inc., a Chicago-based non-profit consulting agency, helped create and organize the National Housing and Human Development Alliance. The file includes some material relating to this organization.
    - 1972 January-June (Box 88, Folder 891)
    - 1972 July - 1974 (Box 88, Folder 892)
    - (Literature), 1971-1974 (Box 89, Folder 893)
  - National Housing Law Project
    - 1987 (Box 89, Folder 894)
    - 1988 (Box 89, Folder 895)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 89, Folder 896)
    - 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 89, Folder 897)
    - 1996-2001 (Box 89, Folder 898)
    - 2002 (Box 89, Folder 899)
    - 2003 (Box 89, Folder 900)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 90, Folder 901)
    - 2006-2007, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 902)
  - National Information Bureau, 1963-1970 (Box 90, Folder 903)
  - National Institute of Labor Education, 1959, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 904)
    Support for residential institutes on race relations for staff members from Southern labor unions.
  - National Institute of Labor Education, 1964-1965 (Box 90, Folder 905)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition
    The National Low Income Housing Coalition was a successor organization to the Low Income Housing Information Service.
    - 1992, 1994-1996 October (Box 90, Folder 906)
    - 1996 November - 1997 (Box 90, Folder 907)
    - 2004 (Box 90, Folder 908)
    - 2005 (Box 90, Folder 909)
      File contains materials relating to the National Housing Voucher Summit.
  - National Puerto Rican/Hispanic Voter Participation Project
    - 1983-1984 (Box 90, Folder 910)
    - 1985 (Box 90, Folder 911)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 912)
  - National Repertory Foundation, 1962, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 913)
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students
    - 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 914)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 91, Folder 915)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 916)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 91, Folder 917)
    - 1970-1972, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 918)
  - National Study Service, 1968-1970 (Box 91, Folder 919)
    Support for study and dissemination of information on changes affecting public welfare policy and programs.
  - National Training and Information Center
    Grants in 1972, 1973, and 1975, were made to the Center for Community Change, to establish a Housing Training and Information Center developed in cooperation with the National People's Action on Housing. The Housing Training and Information Center changed its name to National Training and Information Center in March 1976.
    Gayle Cincotta was executive director of the Chicago-based organization, whose programs targeted redlining and other abusive mortgage lending and foreclosure practices.
    See also files for Center for Community Change.
    - 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 920)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 921)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 922)
    - 1979-1982 (Box 92, Folder 923)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 92, Folder 924)
    - 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 92, Folder 925)
    - 1991-1992 August (Box 92, Folder 926)
    - 1992 September - 1994 (Box 92, Folder 927)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 92, Folder 928)
    - (Literature), 1975-1977 (Box 92, Folder 929)
    - (Literature), 1994, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 930)
      Includes NTIC publication, The Silent Bomb: FHA Devastation of Neighborhoods. A Manual to help communities organize against the abuse of the FHA program. October 1994.
  - National Urban Coalition
    - 1967, 1969-1972, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 931)
    - 1975-1981 (Box 93, Folder 932)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 93, Folder 933)
  - National Urban League: General
    - 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 934)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 935)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 93, Folder 936)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 937)
    - 1969-1970, 1972, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 938)
    - 1975 (Box 93, Folder 939)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 940)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 94, Folder 941)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 94, Folder 942)
    - 1984-1986, 1991-1994 (Box 94, Folder 943)
    - 1995 (Box 94, Folder 944)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 945)
    - 1998-2004 (Box 94, Folder 946)
  - National Urban League: Census Project, 1969-1970 (Box 94, Folder 947)
  - National Urban League: Chicago - West Side Project, 1968-1969 (Box 94, Folder 948)
  - National Urban League: Voter Registration and Citizen Education Program, 1972 - 1973 May (Box 94, Folder 949)
  - National Urban League: Voter Registration and Citizen Education Program, 1973 June -1975, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 950)
  - National Youth Advocacy/Employment Coalition
    Around 1982, the National Youth Advocacy Coalition changed its name to National Youth Employment Coalition.
    - 1979 (Box 95, Folder 951)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 95, Folder 952)
    - 1982, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 953)
  - Natural Area Council, 1966-1973 (Box 95, Folder 954)
  - Natural Area Council, 1974-1975, 1978, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 955)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council
    - 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 956)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 95, Folder 957)
    - 1983-1989 (Box 95, Folder 958)
    - (Legal Briefs), 1981 (Box 95, Folder 959)
      Complaint and memorandum concerning Gateway National Recreation Area and Fort Wadsworth.
  - Nature Conservancy
    Support for conservation internships for inner-city youth.
    - 1995-1996 (Box 96, Folder 960)
    - 1997-2003 (Box 96, Folder 961)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 96, Folder 962)
      Digital media have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - 2004 Summer Internship Program for City Youth: A Day at Otter Creek Preserve in New York, 2012.089.001; 389 Megabytes 1 digital file Imaged from 1 dvd (Item 2012.089.001)
      - Internship Program for City Youth: The 2005 Field Season, 2012.089.002; 656 Megabytes 1 digital file Imaged from 1 dvd (Item 2012.089.002)
  - Neighborhood Day Nursery of Harlem, 1966-1968, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 963)
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project
    - 1996-1997 (Box 96, Folder 964)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 96, Folder 965)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 96, Folder 966)
      - "Free EBT Cash Access Points in the Bronx," and "Bushwick Cooperative FCU Field of Membership" (maps), 2000; 2014:FA407:010; 2 items (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:010)
    - 2003 (Box 96, Folder 967)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 96, Folder 968)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 96, Folder 969)
  - Neighborhood Family Services Coalition / Harlem Children's Zone
    The Harlem Children's Zone (until 2002 known as the Rheedlen Centers for Children and Families) was the fiscal sponsor for the Neighborhood Family Services Coalition. Good Shepherd Services assumed this administrative sponsorship in August 2007.
    - 2000-2005 (Box 97, Folder 970)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 971)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 972)
  - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc.
    - 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 973)
    - 1976-1979 (Box 97, Folder 974)
  - Neighborhood Housing Services of New York City, Inc.
    - 1981-1983 (Box 97, Folder 975)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 97, Folder 976)
    - 1987-1991 (Box 97, Folder 977)
    - 1992-1994 (Box 97, Folder 978)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 97, Folder 979)
    - 1998-2001, 2009 (Box 98, Folder 980)
      The 2009 grant request was declined.
  - Neighborhood Initiatives Development Corporation
    - 1996-1999 (Box 98, Folder 981)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 98, Folder 982)
    - 2003 (Box 98, Folder 983)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 98, Folder 984)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Coalition of New York State, 1995-1996 (Box 98, Folder 985)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment Corporation
    For related materials, see also files for Neighborhood Housing Services of New York City, Inc.
    - 1979-1982 (Box 98, Folder 986)
    - 1985-1990 (Box 98, Folder 987)
  - Neighbors, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 98, Folder 988)
    Neighbors, Inc. was a Washington, D.C. project working to create stable integrated neighborhoods.
  - New School for Social Research (Dorothy Hirshon Fellowship in Urban Affairs and Policy Analysis), 1979-1980 (Box 99, Folder 989)
  - New School University (Milano Graduate School), 2004-2005 (Box 99, Folder 990)
    Grant to support a lecture series at the Milano Graduate School of Management and Urban Policy in memory of Taconic trustee Bill Green.
  - New Thing Art and Architecture Center, 1968-1970, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 991)
  - New York ACORN Housing Company, Inc., 1999 (Box 99, Folder 992)
    The ACORN acronym stands for Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now.
  - New York ACORN Schools Office
    - 1996 January-March (Box 99, Folder 993)
    - 1996 April - 1997 (Box 99, Folder 994)
  - New York City: Board of Education
    - 1959, 1966-1969 (Box 99, Folder 995)
    - 1975-1976, 1986, 1993-1995 (Box 99, Folder 996)
  - New York City: City Planning Commission, 1959-1965 (Box 99, Folder 997)
    Support for professional assistance and URBANDOC project.
  - New York City: Department of Employment
    Folder title carried additional description, 1984 Tax Levy Initiative for Youth. Correspondence and proposals, involving Community Service Society, Stanley S. Litow, and Commissioner Ronald T. Gault.
    - 1984 January-July (Box 99, Folder 998)
    - 1984 August-September (Box 99, Folder 999)